Tell me this Ashish Chaturmohata,
if you look at Ashish, your first question is about
girls
and Vijendra, my hobby is TI
Industries and I think on a
large account, on the inverted shoulder,
minister chart day, a festival, now it is
trading at the support level of 3270, here you should take a
long with a stop loss of 3220,
I am more inclined to
come in the stock of Side Industries,
remember Piya Industries is a very good
student and there is a very good crowd in
quantum breakout in it and now
on the back foot after failure, Sachin, your fix is
single,
increase in etc. Group A Shady
Plot Cast Defense seems interesting to me,
here it is already canvas and definition on the 30-minute chart,
today in this way
a base has formed here around 12 so
Hitesh has given a reversal, the
way it reaches its, then I think
for intraday this momentum you have got should be
feeling around 1270, the
reversal will be great at 1310  The
target will be 2017, you have to place a stop loss
and end buy at 2002, keep in mind the
age of Aanchal
or you can decide to place a single stock.
Now I will talk about the
rise in Piya Industries.
ICICI Lombard has a call to make a rise with
your screen. Meanwhile, Satpute
is preparing to make a clear save. Subscribe,
see on Monday we had talked about
crossing that Reliance is working under the
average given pattern here
after Krishna, so when Reliance buys at the
price of 282, we had hit the support of 2565 here, so
when you
buy, you will have two stop losses, it will come to 2550, there is a
slight day problem and Shetty should buy
Reliance with a stop loss of 125 to 150,
its target should be 2650, so
from here at least 6270 office will
come to me in the center, so a
call to buy Reliance Industries, rest ICICI Bank
Reliance is two interesting  Stop patterns
came on the radar as soon as it opened and Reliance
is an attractive idea for singles, the desire to buy Kharbe
is 2650, if the wait is going to last then there is
no need to panic, for this you can
go ahead, Reliance has already been discussed, the channel is
owned and managed by Reliance Industries, if you are
thinking of buying then
definitely consult an advisor and
despite the virus today, any single, any museum and gallery
specializes in banks, a long test will
come because if you see, Lal Saini
Amit and consolidation saw that the
network is formed here, today look at Facebook above 84, then
buy in the bank on current news, stop
classes will be there, there is a risk of ₹10, you
can see 8 end effective on the upward direction and the options
can be reversed, Admani call option is ₹800 ₹50,
take it for buying there with immediate effect, here you have to
buy from the establishment of Bare after 30 minutes
two